Calvin Tomkins Papers
The Museum of Modern Art, Publisher
- Series V: Audio Recordings, 1962-2006
  - Gursky (4), 11/2/2000 (Box 72, Cassette V.160)
    RadioShack XR 90
  - Gursky (5), 11/4/2000 (Box 72, Cassette V.161)
  - Thomas Struth, 11/15/2000 (Box 72, Cassette V.162)
  - Thomas Demand, 12/2/2000 (Box 72, Cassette V.163)
  - Gursky, 12/10/2000; Cassette marked: "Gursky on Thomas Demand" (Box 72, Cassette V.164)
  - Julian Schnabel (1), 1/23/2001; Cassette marked: "Julian (1) Javier Bardem" (Box 72, Cassette V.165)
  - Julian Schnabel (2), 1/23/2001 (Box 72, Cassette V.166)
  - John Killick & JS (3), 1/25/2001 (Box 72, Cassette V.167)
  - Julian (4), ca. 2001 (Box 72, Cassette V.168)
  - Julian (5), ca. 2001 (Box 72, Cassette V.169)
  - Julian (6), 1/23-1/27/2001; Side A: "-103 JS 1/23/2001; 103-end JS 1/27/2001" (Box 72, Cassette V.170)
  - Julian (7), ca. 2001 (Box 72, Cassette V.171)
  - JS (8), ca. 2001 (Box 73, Cassette V.172)
  - Van Gogh Press Preview, 2/1/2001 (Box 73, Cassette V.173)
    Maxell Instant Start Series C30
  - J.S. (9) Albany Tapes, 2/6-2/7/2001; "Trip to Albany - 2/6-7/2001" (Box 73, Cassette V.174)
  - Julian (10) Albany Tapes, ca. 2/7/2001; "Albany to NY on train" (Box 73, Cassette V.175)
  - JS (11) Albany Tapes, ca. 2/7/2001; "Train to NY (to 169 only)" (Box 73, Cassette V.176)
  - Julian (12) Montauk, 2/8/2001; "Car to Montauk" (Box 73, Cassette V.177)
  - Julian (13) Montauk, ca. 2/8/2001 (Box 73, Cassette V.178)
  - Ingrid Sischy, 2/16/2001 (Box 73, Cassette V.179)
  - David Salle, 2/28/2001 (Box 73, Cassette V.180)
  - "Van Gogh's Portraits of Joseph Roulin", 3/6/2001; Lecture by Kirk Varnedoe at MoMA; See also Sound Recordings of Museum-Related Events, 2001.54, for additional copies of this recording. (Box 73, Cassette V.181)
    Maxell UR 90
  - Kirk Varnedoe (1), 4/12/2001; , 4/16/2001 (Box 73, Cassette V.182)
    RadioShack XR-90
  - Varnedoe (2), 4/16/2001; , 4/24/2001 (Box 73, Cassette V.183)
  - Varnedoe (3), n.d. (Box 73, Cassette V.184)
  - Frank Stella, 4/19/2001 (Box 73, Cassette V.185)
  - Deitch, 4/20/2001 (Box 73, Cassette V.186)
  - Rosenblum, 4/20/2001 (Box 73, Cassette V.187)
  - Glenn Lowry, 4/24/2001 (Box 73, Cassette V.188)
  - Peter Galassi, 4/26/2001 (Box 73, Cassette V.189)
  - Sam Varnedoe, 4/30/2001 (Box 74, Cassette V.190)
  - Aggie Gund, 4/30/2001 (Box 74, Cassette V.191)
  - Terry Riley, 5/2001 (Box 74, Cassette V.192)
  - Varnedoe (4), 5/2/2001 (Box 74, Cassette V.193)
  - Kirk [Varnedoe] (5), n.d. (Box 74, Cassette V.194)
  - Varnedoe (6), n.d. (Box 74, Cassette V.195)
  - Jeffrey Weiss, 5/3/2001 (Box 74, Cassette V.196)
  - Robert Storr, 5/4/2001 (Box 74, Cassette V.197)
    RadioShack XR-0
  - Elyn Z. [Zimmerman], 5/4/2001 (Box 74, Cassette V.198)
  - Rusty Powell; Ronald Lauder, 5/16/2001; , 5/29/2001 (Box 74, Cassette V.199)
  - Dick Oldenburg, 5/16/2001 (Box 74, Cassette V.200)
  - Adam Gopnik, 5/29/2001 (Box 74, Cassette V.201)
  - Ronald Lauder/Carolyn Lauchner, 5/30/2001 (Box 74, Cassette V.202)
  - Ann Umland; Chuck Close, 5/31/2001; , 6/6/2001 (Box 74, Cassette V.203)
  - Jerry Neuner, 6/6/2001 (Box 74, Cassette V.204)
  - S. Lane Faison (1), 6/14/2001 (Box 74, Cassette V.205)
  - Lane Faison (2), n.d. (Box 74, Cassette V.206)
  - Kirk Varnedoe 7, 6/18/2001 (Box 74, Cassette V.207)
  - John Elderfield; Mary Lee Bandy, 6/19/2001 (Box 75, Cassette V.208)
  - Mary Lee Bandy, 6/19/2001 (Box 75, Cassette V.209)
  - Patterson Sims, 6/26/2001 (Box 75, Cassette V.210)
  - Nan Rosenthal, 6/28/2001 (Box 75, Cassette V.211)
  - Ellen Phelan, 7/25/2001 (Box 75, Cassette V.212)
  - Charles Stuckey on Kirk [Varnedoe], 8/2/2001 (Box 75, Cassette V.213)
  - Ellen Phelan, 8/4/2001 (Box 75, Cassette V.214)
  - Chuck Close, 8/12/2001 (Box 75, Cassette V.215)
  - Robert Storr on Ellen Phelan, 8/14/2001 (Box 75, Cassette V.216)
  - Chip Benson, 8/16/2001 (Box 75, Cassette V.217)
  - Jim Cuno, 8/20/2001 (Box 75, Cassette V.218)
  - Kirk Varnedoe (8), 9/5/2001 (Box 75, Cassette V.219)
  - Ellen Phelan, 9/22/2001 (Box 75, Cassette V.220)
  - Varnedoe (10), 9/24/2001; There is no extant cassette labeled Kirk Varnedoe (9) (Box 75, Cassette V.221)
  - Robt. Brustein, 9/27/2001 (Box 75, Cassette V.222)
  - Jeremy Knowles; Matt Saunder, 9/27/2001; , 10/6/2001 (Box 75, Cassette V.223)
  - Scott Rothkopf/James Cuno, 9/28/2001 (Box 75, Cassette V.224)
  - WTC interview w/Artists, ca. 10/2001 (Box 75, Cassette V.225)
  - Chris Killip, 10/4/2001 (Box 75, Cassette V.226)
  - Ellen Phelan 4, 10/12/2001 (Box 76, Cassette V.227)
  - Ellen Phelan (5), 10/14/2001 (Box 76, Cassette V.228)
  - Rob Storr, 10/15/2001; Side A: "On Phelan/Harvard" Side B: "115 - Eva Hesse" (Box 76, Cassette V.229)
  - Phelan (5) Cont., 10/16/2001; Cassette marked 10/14 (Box 76, Cassette V.230)
  - Sol Lewitt, 10/19/2001 (Box 76, Cassette V.231)
  - Alfred Guzzetti, 10/19/2001 (Box 76, Cassette V.232)
  - Susan Fonter, 12/5/2001 (Box 76, Cassette V.233)
  - Davi Rosenheek, 12/5/2001 (Box 76, Cassette V.234)
  - Neil Rudenstine, 12/5/2001 (Box 76, Cassette V.235)
  - Susan Fonter II, 12/11/2001 (Box 76, Cassette V.236)
  - [Richard] Serra (1), 1/10/2002 (Box 76, Cassette V.237)
  - Richard Koshalek; Matthew Barney, 1/30/2002; , 1/31/2002 (Box 76, Cassette V.238)
    RadioShack XR-120
  - Serra (2), 2/6/2002 (Box 76, Cassette V.239)
  - Serra (3), 2/6/2002 (Box 76, Cassette V.240)
  - Ashton Hawkins, 2/6/2002 (Box 76, Cassette V.241)
    RadioShack HC-90
  - Brice Marden; Richard Gluckman, 1/30, 2/7/2002 (Box 76, Cassette V.242)
  - Serra (4), 2/8/2002 (Box 76, Cassette V.243)
  - Serra (5), n.d. (Box 76, Cassette V.244)
  - Elizabeth Murray; Lynne Coate, n.d.; , 2/13/2002 (Box 76, Cassette V.245)
  - Emily Pulitzer, 2/13/2002 (Box 77, Cassette V.246)
  - Phil Glass; Chuck Close, 2/14/2002; , 2/27/2002 (Box 77, Cassette V.247)
  - Kirk Varnedoe, 2/14/2002 (Box 77, Cassette V.248)
  - Frank Gehry, 2/14/2002 (Box 77, Cassette V.249)
  - Serra (6), 2/15/2002 (Box 77, Cassette V.250)
  - Joe Helman, 2/20/2002 (Box 77, Cassette V.251)
  - Joan Jonas; Susan Brundage, 2/21/2002 (Box 77, Cassette V.252)
  - John Silberman; Nancy Holt, 2/22/2002; , 3/26/2002 (Box 77, Cassette V.253)
  - Serra (7), 2/27/2002 (Box 77, Cassette V.254)
  - Doug Christmas, 2/27/2002 (Box 77, Cassette V.255)
  - Joel Shapiro, 2/28/2002 (Box 77, Cassette V.256)
  - Trina McKeever; Clare Serra Weyergraf, 3/6/2002 (Box 77, Cassette V.257)
  - Ealan Wingate, 3/7/2002 (Box 77, Cassette V.258)
  - Serra (8) (Beacon), 3/8/2002 (Box 77, Cassette V.259)
  - J. Johns - Serra (9) (cont.), 3/27/2002; , n.d. (Box 77, Cassette V.260)
  - Serra (9), 4/5/2002 (Box 77, Cassette V.261)
  - Carmen Gimenez, 5/7/2002 (Box 77, Cassette V.262)
    RadioShack XR-60
  - [James] Turrell (1), 5/15/2002 (Box 77, Cassette V.263)
  - Turrell (2), n.d. (Box 78, Cassette V.264)
  - Turell (3), n.d. (Box 78, Cassette V.265)
  - Turrell (4), n.d. (Box 78, Cassette V.266)
  - Turrell (5), n.d. (Box 78, Cassette V.267)
  - Richard Koshalek, 5/26/2002 (Box 78, Cassette V.268)
  - Walter Hopps; Turrell (6), 5/29/2002; , n.d. (Box 78, Cassette V.269)
  - Turrell (6) @Mattress Factory, 5/31/2002 (Box 78, Cassette V.270)
  - Turrell @Mattress Factory, 6/1/2002 (Box 78, Cassette V.271)
  - Barbara Ludrowsky; Helen Winkler, 6/1/2002; , 6/19/2002 (Box 78, Cassette V.272)
  - Merce Cunningham, 6/7/2002 (Box 78, Cassette V.273)
  - Michael Govan, 6/12/2002 (Box 78, Cassette V.274)
  - Kate Ganz/Elyn Zimmerman; John Coplans, 6/13/2002; , 6/14/2002 (Box 78, Cassette V.275)
  - Lucy Shelton; Alana Heiss (1), 6/19/2002; , 6/21/2002 (Box 78, Cassette V.276)
    RadioShack
  - Alana Heiss (2); Jane Livingston, 6/21/2002; , 6/25/2002 (Box 78, Cassette V.277)
  - Robt Wilson @Watermill, 8/1/2002 (Box 78, Cassette V.278)
  - Michael Govan, 9/3/2002 (Box 78, Cassette V.279)
  - Turrell, 9/10/2002 (Box 78, Cassette V.280)
  - Chelsea Romersa, 9/16/2002 (Box 78, Cassette V.281)
  - Nancy Spector; Robert Irwin (re: Turrell), 9/20/2002; , 9/21/2002 (Box 79, Cassette V.282)
  - Neville Wakefield, 10/7/2002 (Box 79, Cassette V.283)
  - Barbara Gladstone, 10/15/2002 (Box 79, Cassette V.284)
  - Rob Storr re: MB, 10/16/2002 (Box 79, Cassette V.285)
  - Leo Villareal; Richard Flood, 10/16/2002; , 11/7/2002 (Box 79, Cassette V.286)
  - Hilton Als; Shawn Caley, 10/17/2002; , 11/6/2002 (Box 79, Cassette V.287)
  - Matthew Barney (1), 10/21/2002 (Box 79, Cassette V.288)
  - Hans Ulrich; James Lingwood, 10/21/2002; , 10/23/2002 (Box 79, Cassette V.289)
  - Barney (2), 10/23/2002 (Box 79, Cassette V.290)
  - MB [Barney] (3), 10/23/2002 (Box 79, Cassette V.291)
  - MB [Barney] (4), n.d. (Box 79, Cassette V.292)
  - MB [Barney] (5), 10/25/2002 (Box 79, Cassette V.293)
  - Aime Mullins, 11/7/2002 (Box 79, Cassette V.294)
  - Michael Govan (2), 11/12/2002 (Box 79, Cassette V.295)
    RadioShack HC090
  - Robert Barney; Gabe Bartalos, 11/13/2002; , 11/14/2002 (Box 79, Cassette V.296)
  - Gabe Bartalos (cont.); Keith Edmier, 11/14/2002; , 11/22/2002 (Box 79, Cassette V.297)
  - Alice Aycock; Norman Mailer, 11/15/2002; , 11/21/2002 (Box 79, Cassette V.298)
  - Jonathan Bepler, 11/15/2002 (Box 79, Cassette V.299)
  - Marcia Barney, 11/17/2002 (Box 80, Cassette V.300)
  - Michael Rees, 11/18/2002 (Box 80, Cassette V.301)
  - MB [Barney] (6), 11/19/2002 (Box 80, Cassette V.302)
  - Matt Ryle, 11/19/2002 (Box 80, Cassette V.303)
  - MB [Barney] (7), 11/20/2002 (Box 80, Cassette V.304)
    RadioShack HD-90
  - Mark Gonzalez, 11/22/2002 (Box 80, Cassette V.305)
  - Govan (3), 1/9/2003 (Box 80, Cassette V.306)
  - Virginia Devan, 1/23/2003 (Box 80, Cassette V.307)
  - Margaret Douglas Hamilton; Lynne Cooke, 2/10/2003; , 2/11/2003 (Box 80, Cassette V.308)
  - Lois de Menil, 2/11/2003 (Box 80, Cassette V.309)
  - Bill & Patti Dilworth; Bob Irwin, 2/14/2003; , 2/16/2003; Cassette marked: "Bill Dilworth (Earth Room); Patti Dilworth (Broken Kilo)" (Box 80, Cassette V.310)
  - Govan (4), 2/15/2003 (Box 80, Cassette V.311)
  - Govan (5), 2/15/2003 (Box 80, Cassette V.312)
  - Bob Whitman; Patrick Lannan, 2/19/2003; , 4/4/2003 (Box 80, Cassette V.313)
  - Richard Gluckman, 2/25/2003 (Box 80, Cassette V.314)
  - Charles Wright, 2/25/2003 (Box 80, Cassette V.315)
  - Fredrika Hunter, n.d. (Box 80, Cassette V.316)
  - Heiner Friedrich, 3/3/2003 (Box 80, Cassette V.317)
  - Len Riggio, 3/10/2003 (Box 81, Cassette V.318)
  - Marfa, 3/15/2003; , 3/16/2003 (Box 81, Cassette V.319)
  - Helen Winkler, 3/16/2003; , 3/17/2003 (Box 81, Cassette V.320)
  - Govan (6); Fred Sandback, 3/19/2003 (Box 81, Cassette V.321)
  - Heiner Friedrich, 3/20/2003 (Box 81, Cassette V.322)
  - John Chamberlain, 3/21/2003 (Box 81, Cassette V.323)
  - Marukh Targsor, 4/15/2003 (Box 81, Cassette V.324)
    TDK DR-I 90
  - Willy Van Ness, n.d. (Box 81, Cassette V.325)
  - Fariha Friedrich, 4/22/2003 (Box 81, Cassette V.326)
  - Tom & Jane Doyle, 5/8/2003 (Box 81, Cassette V.327)
  - Elizabeth Smith, 5/8/2003 (Box 81, Cassette V.328)
  - Valerie Giles, 5/15/2003 (Box 81, Cassette V.329)
  - Mona Hadler, 5/15/2003 (Box 81, Cassette V.330)
  - [Lee] Bontecou (1), n.d. (Box 81, Cassette V.331)
  - Bontecou (2), n.d. (Box 81, Cassette V.332)
  - Bontecou (3), n.d. (Box 81, Cassette V.333)
  - Bontecou (4), 5/22/2003 (Box 81, Cassette V.334)
  - Barbara Castelli, 5/27/2003 (Box 81, Cassette V.335)
  - Tony Ganz, 6/1/2003 (Box 82, Cassette V.336)
  - Lois Dodd, 6/3/2003; Cassette case marked "Judith Goldman/Anne Friedman" (n.d.), while the cassette itself is marked in Dodd's name. (Box 82, Cassette V.337)
  - Bontecou (5), 6/6/2003 (Box 82, Cassette V.338)
  - Bontecou (6); Bill Giles, 6/6, 6/7/2003 (Box 82, Cassette V.339)
  - Bill Giles and Lee Bontecou, 6/7/2003 (Box 82, Cassette V.340)
  - Anne Philbin, 6/9/2003 (Box 82, Cassette V.341)
  - Daniel Weinberg, 6/10/2003 (Box 82, Cassette V.342)
  - Michael Rosenfeld, Hallie Harrisburg, 6/16/2003 (Box 82, Cassette V.343)
  - Christos [Jeanne-Claude and Christo] (1), 8/12/2003 (Box 82, Cassette V.344)
  - Cai Guo-Qiang, 9/3/2003 (Box 82, Cassette V.345)
  - Ted Kheel, 11/3/2003 (Box 82, Cassette V.346)
  - Christos (2), 11/9/2003 (Box 82, Cassette V.347)
  - Vince Davenport, 11/10/2003 (Box 82, Cassette V.348)
  - Gordon Davis; Patricia Harris, 11/12/2003; , 12/5/2003 (Box 82, Cassette V.349)
  - Al Maysles; Kate Levin, 11/15/2003; , 1/26/2004; Cassette case marked only "Al Maysles 11/15/2003" (Box 82, Cassette V.350)
  - Betsy Barlow Rogers; Richard Gilder, 11/20/2003; , 1/15/2004 (Box 82, Cassette V.351)
  - Evelyn Lauder; Regine Peruggi, 11/24/2003; , 12/5/2003 (Box 82, Cassette V.352)
  - Wolfgang Volz; Adrian Benepe, 11/25/2003; , 12/5/2003 (Box 82, Cassette V.353)
  - Doug Blonsky; Henry Stern, 12/11/2003; , 1/15/2004 (Box 83, Cassette V.354)
  - Aggie Gund; Scott Hodes, 12/11/2003; , 1/29/2004 (Box 83, Cassette V.355)
    Sony HF 60
  - [Philippe] de Montebello et al.; Mayor Bloomsberg @News Conference, 12/19/2003; , 1/22/2004; Cassette actually marked "1/22/2003" Side A: "de Montebello et al." Side B: "Bloomberg, Benepe, Christos Press Conf." (Box 83, Cassette V.356)
  - Eugene McCarthy (1), 12/30/2003 (Box 83, Cassette V.357)
  - Eugene McCarthy (2), 12/30/2003 (Box 83, Cassette V.358)
  - Christos (3), 1/11/2004 (Box 83, Cassette V.359)
  - Christos (4), 1/11/2004 (Box 83, Cassette V.360)
  - Christos (4), n.d. (Box 83, Cassette V.361)
  - Christos (4), 1/23/2004 (Box 83, Cassette V.362)
  - Christos (5), 2/2/2004 (Box 83, Cassette V.363)
  - Glenn Lowry, 2/2/2004 (Box 83, Cassette V.364)
  - James Coddington on "Demoiselles", MoMA, 4/21/2004 (Box 83, Cassette V.365)
  - John Elderfield on "Demoiselles", 4/23/2004 (Box 83, Cassette V.366)
  - Altman (1), 4/27/2004 (Box 83, Cassette V.367)
  - Massimiliano on Maurizio C. [Cattelan], 5/12/2004 (Box 83, Cassette V.368)
  - Altman (2), 5/14/2004 (Box 83, Cassette V.369)
  - Altman (1), 5/14/2004 (Box 83, Cassette V.370)
  - Maurizio Cattelan (2), 5/24/2004 (Box 83, Cassette V.371)
    RadioShack LN-90
  - Maurizio Cattelan (2), 5/25/2004; Cassette case marked "5/24/2005" (Box 84, Cassette V.372)
  - Maurizio Cattelan (3), 5/25/2004 (Box 84, Cassette V.373)
  - Emanuel Perrotin, 5/29/2004 (Box 84, Cassette V.374)
  - Ali Subotnik, 5/31/2004 (Box 84, Cassette V.375)
  - Jeffrey Deitch, 6/2/2004; Cassette marked "Laura Hoptman 6/8/2004" (Box 84, Cassette V.376)
  - Jeffrey Deitch, 6/2/2004 (Box 84, Cassette V.377)
  - Marian Goodman, 6/7/2004 (Box 84, Cassette V.378)
  - Laura Hauptman; Elizabeth Peyton, 6/10/2004; , 6/21/2004 (Box 84, Cassette V.379)
  - Maurizio, Paris, 6/14/2004 (Box 84, Cassette V.380)
  - Rirkrit (?) Tiraranga; Hans Obrist; MC - Paris, 6/14/2004 (Box 84, Cassette V.381)
  - Maurizio @Beaux Arts and @Cafe Flore, 6/15/2004 (Box 84, Cassette V.382)
  - Maurizio - Paris (Clichy), 6/15/2004; , 6/16/2004 (Box 84, Cassette V.383)
  - Catherine Ceremie; Gabriel Orozco, 6/16/2004; , 6/17/2004 (Box 84, Cassette V.384)
  - Maurizio - on the Quai, 6/16/2004; , 6/17/2004 (Box 84, Cassette V.385)
  - Hans Ulrich Obrist & Dominique Gonzalez-Foerster, 6/17/2004 (Box 84, Cassette V.386)
  - Massimo di Carlo; Massimiliano Gione, 6/23/2004 (Box 84, Cassette V.387)
  - Chrissie Isles, 6/24/2004 (Box 84, Cassette V.388)
  - Francesco Bonami, 6/26/2004 (Box 84, Cassette V.389)
  - Maurizio, 7/10/2004 (Box 84, Cassette V.390)
  - Maurizio (cont.), 7/10/2004 (Box 84, Cassette V.391)
  - David White, 11/4/2004 (Box 85, Cassette V.392)
  - Paul Schimmel, 11/14/2004 (Box 85, Cassette V.393)
  - Bob Rauschenberg (1), 12/12/2004 (Box 85, Cassette V.394)
  - Bob Rauschenberg (2), 12/12/2004; , 12/13/2004 (Box 85, Cassette V.395)
  - Bob Rauschenberg (3), 12/13/2004 (Box 85, Cassette V.396)
  - Susan Davidson, 12/21/2004 (Box 85, Cassette V.397)
  - Jasper Johns, 12/28/2004 (Box 85, Cassette V.398)
  - Adam Weinberg (1), 12/30/2004 (Box 85, Cassette V.399)
  - Adam Weinberg (2), 12/30/2004 (Box 85, Cassette V.400)
  - Chris Rauschenberg; Trisha Brown, 1/5/2005; , 1/10/2005 (Box 85, Cassette V.401)
  - John Elderfield, 1/13/2005 (Box 85, Cassette V.402)
  - Antonio Homem, 1/13/2005 (Box 85, Cassette V.403)
  - Michael Govan, 1/14/2005 (Box 85, Cassette V.404)
  - Darryl Pattorf, 1/14/2005 (Box 85, Cassette V.405)
  - Jim Rosenquist, 1/19/2005 (Box 85, Cassette V.406)
  - Jeff Koons; Jeffrey Deitch, 1/21/2005; , 1/22/2005 (Box 85, Cassette V.407)
  - [Jeffrey] Deitch (2), 1/22/2005 (Box 85, Cassette V.408)
  - Anne Glimcher, 1/24/2005 (Box 86, Cassette V.409)
  - Joachim Pissarro, 1/26/2005 (Box 86, Cassette V.410)
  - Leo Steinberg, 2/9/2005 (Box 86, Cassette V.411)
  - [Robert] Rauschenberg, 2/22/2005 (Box 86, Cassette V.412)
  - Rirkrit [Tiravanija] (1), 3/2/2005 (Box 86, Cassette V.413)
  - Gavin Brown, 3/9/2005 (Box 86, Cassette V.414)
  - Rirkrit (2), 3/14/2005 (Box 86, Cassette V.415)
  - Liz Linden, 3/19/2005 (Box 86, Cassette V.416)
  - Ann Temkin on Rikrit, 3/21/2005 (Box 86, Cassette V.417)
  - Laura Hoptman, 3/22/2005 (Box 86, Cassette V.418)
  - Keith Christiansen; Dorothy Mahon, 3/22/2005; , 4/6/2005 (Box 86, Cassette V.419)
  - Rirkrit (3), 3/23/2005 (Box 86, Cassette V.420)
  - Joan Young [on Rikrit], 3/24/2005 (Box 86, Cassette V.421)
  - Elizabeth Peyton, 3/24/2005 (Box 86, Cassette V.422)
  - John Kessler, 3/31/2005 (Box 86, Cassette V.423)
  - Adam Weinberg (3), 4/4/2005 (Box 86, Cassette V.424)
  - Philippe de Montebello; George Visacea, 4/6/2005 (Box 86, Cassette V.425)
  - Thelma Golden, 4/7/2005 (Box 86, Cassette V.426)
  - Philippe Perreno; Glenn Lowry re: David Rockefeller, 4/7/2005; , 5/17/2005 (Box 87, Cassette V.427)
  - Nicholas Hall, 4/11/2005 (Box 87, Cassette V.428)
  - Keith Christiansen (2), 4/12/2005 (Box 87, Cassette V.429)
  - Keith Christiansen (3), 5/2/2005 (Box 87, Cassette V.430)
  - Rirkrit (4), 5/12/2005 (Box 87, Cassette V.431)
  - David Rockefeller, 5/13/2005 (Box 87, Cassette V.432)
  - Bruce Ferguson, 5/17/2005 (Box 87, Cassette V.433)
  - Rirkrit (5), 5/18/2005 (Box 87, Cassette V.434)
  - Amanda - Everett Fahy; Rochelle Steiner, 5/19/2005 (Box 87, Cassette V.435)
  - Nancy Spector, 5/23/2005 (Box 87, Cassette V.436)
  - Molly Nesbitt, 6/6/2005 (Box 87, Cassette V.437)
  - Antoinette Gurel, 6/6/2005 (Box 87, Cassette V.438)
  - Rirkrit (6), 6/8/2005 (Box 87, Cassette V.439)
  - Rirkrit (6), [6/8/2005] (Box 87, Cassette V.440)
  - Liam Gillick, 6/13/2005 (Box 87, Cassette V.441)
  - Adam Weinberg (4), 6/20/2005 (Box 87, Cassette V.442)
  - Eric Parker, 6/22/2005 (Box 87, Cassette V.443)
  - Rochelle Steiner; Francesca Grass, 7/1/2005; , 7/3/2005 (Box 87, Cassette V.444)
  - Rirkrit (London) (7), 7/2/2005; , 7/3/2005 (Box 88, Cassette V.445)
  - Hans Ulrich Obrist, 7/3/2005 (Box 88, Cassette V.446)
  - Rirkrit (8); Gavin Brown, 7/4/2005 (Box 88, Cassette V.447)
  - David Ross; Richard Flood, 7/22/2005 (Box 88, Cassette V.448)
  - Rikrit, 8/29/2005 (Box 88, Cassette V.449)
  - Elisabeth Sussman, 9/14/2005 (Box 88, Cassette V.450)
  - B. Haskell, 9/15/2005 (Box 88, Cassette V.451)
  - Jennifer Russell, 9/16/2005 (Box 88, Cassette V.452)
  - Carol Mancusi-Ungaro, 9/19/2005 (Box 88, Cassette V.453)
  - Renzo Piano, 9/21/2005 (Box 88, Cassette V.454)
  - B. Haskell (2), 9/21/2005 (Box 88, Cassette V.455)
  - Lorraine, 9/26/2005 (Box 88, Cassette V.456)
  - Donna di Salvo, 9/27/2005 (Box 88, Cassette V.457)
  - Tom Armstrong, 9/27/2005 (Box 88, Cassette V.458)
  - Milton & Mickey Freedman, 10/3/2005 (Box 88, Cassette V.459)
  - Max Anderson, 10/4/2005 (Box 88, Cassette V.460)
  - Chuck Close, 10/5/2005 (Box 88, Cassette V.461)
  - David Ross, 10/7/2005 (Box 88, Cassette V.462)
  - Chrissie Isles, 10/11/2005 (Box 88, Cassette V.463)
  - Leonard Lauder; Flora Biddle, 10/19/2005 (Box 88, Cassette V.464)
  - Weinbergs (Jim and Bunny), 10/20/2005 (Box 89, Cassette V.465)
  - Philippe Vergne, 10/22/2005 (Box 89, Cassette V.466)
  - Adam [Weinberg] - Tuttle Installation at the Whitney, 11/3/2005 (Box 89, Cassette V.467)
  - Adam [Weinberg] (5), 11/10/2005 (Box 89, Cassette V.468)
  - Adam [Weinberg] (6), 11/15/2005 (Box 89, Cassette V.469)
  - Adam [Weinberg] (7), 11/22/2005 (Box 89, Cassette V.470)
  - Adam [Weinberg] (8), 12/7/2005 (Box 89, Cassette V.471)
  - Barnaby Furnas, 2/6/2006 (Box 89, Cassette V.472)
  - Jeffrey Weiss; Leo Steinberg, 2/20/2006; , 2/22/2006 (Box 89, Cassette V.473)
  - School Days (2), n.d.; Tape likely made for Talk piece, "Dept. of Precocity: Artists in Their Youth," 2/27/2006 (Box 89, Cassette V.474)
  - J. Johns (1), 2/28/2006 (Box 89, Cassette V.475)
  - Jasper Johns (2), 3/1/2006 (Box 89, Cassette V.476)
  - J. Johns (3), 3/1/2006 (Box 89, Cassette V.477)
  - J. Johns (4), 3/2/2006 (Box 89, Cassette V.478)
  - Jeffrey Deitch, 3/18/2006 (Box 89, Cassette V.479)
  - Jeffrey Weiss, 5/4/2006 (Box 89, Cassette V.480)
  - Johns (5), 5/12/2006 (Box 89, Cassette V.481)
  - Johns (6), 5/12/2006 (Box 89, Cassette V.482)
  - Michael Fitzgerald; David Salle, 5/17/2006; , 7/22/2006 (Box 89, Cassette V.483)
  - Terry Riley (2); George Condo, 5/23/2006; , 6/16/2006 (Box 89, Cassette V.484)
  - Robert Menschel, 6/15/2006 (Box 90, Cassette V.485)
  - Kathy Halbreich, 6/16/2006 (Box 90, Cassette V.486)
  - Johns (6), 7/23/2006 (Box 90, Cassette V.487)
  - Johns (7), 7/23/2006 (Box 90, Cassette V.488)
  - Johns (8), 7/23/2006 (Box 90, Cassette V.489)
  - John Currin, 8/24/2006 (Box 90, Cassette V.490)
  - George Condo, 9/26/2006 (Box 90, Cassette V.491)
  - Merce Cunningham on J.J., 9/27/2006 (Box 90, Cassette V.492)
  - Roberta Bernstein, 9/28/2006 (Box 90, Cassette V.493)
  - Condo, Cattelan, Gioni, 9/28/2006 (Box 90, Cassette V.494)
  - Cattelman, Furnas, and Condo on Jasper Johns, 10/26/2006 (Box 90, Cassette V.495)
  - Jeffrey Deitch and Julian Lethbridge on Johns, 11/1/2006 (Box 90, Cassette V.496)
  - Francis Naumann on J.J., 11/3/2006 (Box 90, Cassette V.497)
  - J. Johns (9), 11/5/2006 (Box 90, Cassette V.498)
Box and Folder List
File numbers marked by an asterisk (*) indicate oversize material that has been separated to the end of the collection.
Researchers should include the asterisk when issuing a request for such material.
I 1-13 1
I 14-22 2
I 23-30 3
I 31-37 4
I 38-44 5
I 45-54 6
I 55-63 7
I 64-71 8
I 72-78 9
I 79-85 10
I 86-89 11
II.A 1-16 12
II.A 17-28 13
II.A 29-41 14
II.A 42-51 15
II.A 52-62 16
II.A 63-71 17
II.A 72-81 18
II.A 82-91 19
II.A 92-99 20
II.A 100-108 21
II.A 109-117 22
II.A 118-127 23
II.A 128-137 24
II.A 138-146 25
II.A 147-154 26
II.A 155-164 27
II.A 165-173 28
II.A 174-179 29
II.B 1-14 30
II.B 15-28 31
II.B 29-39 32
II.B 40-46 33
II.B 47-53 34
II.B 54-59 35
II.B 60-66 36
II.B 67-70 37
III 1-10 38
III 11-22 39
III 23-37 40
III 38-51 41
III 52-65 42
III 66-81 43
III 82-104 44
III 105-130 45
III 131-156 46
IV.A 1 47
IV.B 1-9
IV.B 10-18 48
IV.B 19-29 49
IV.B 30-36 50
IV.B 37-47 51
IV.C 1-28 52
IV.C 29-49 53
IV.C 50-61 54
IV.D 1-11 55
IV.D 12-20 56
IV.D 21-29 57
IV.D 30-39 58
IV.D 40-50 59
IV.D 51-59 60
IV.D 60-67 61
IV.D 68-69* 92
IV.E 1-4* 91
V 1-3, 9 62
V 4-8, 10-22 63
V 23-40 64
V 41-59 65
V 60-79 66
V 80-99 67
V 100-117 68
V 118-135 69
V 136-153 70
V 154-171 71
V 172-189 72
V 190-207 73
V 208-226 74
V 227-245 75
V 246-263 76
V 264-281 77
V 282-299 78
V 300-317 79
V 318-335 80
V 336-353 81
V 354-371 82
V 372-391 83
V 392-408 84
V 409-426 85
V 427-444 86
V 445-464 87
V 465-484 88
V 485-498 89
IV.D 68-69* 90 (Oversized)
IV.E 1-4* 91 (Oversized)